Call Toll-Free

[

](https://m.facebook.com/lifeprotect247)[

](https://mobile.twitter.com/lifeprotect247)[

](https://m.youtube.com/channel/UCBOiF2wHeFCVOPlOBQCKV5w?reload=9&skip_registered_account_check=true)

Home

Our Products

About UsReviewsBlogFAQHelp

Home

Our Products

About Us

Reviews

Blog

FAQ

Help

Privacy Policy
--------------

**Privacy Policy**

 This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their personally identifiable information (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your personally identifiable information in accordance with our website.

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website or app?**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information, social security number or other details to help you with your experience. Additionally, we passively collect information about our visitors using cookies, as set out below.

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, Use Live Chat, Open a Support Ticket or enter information on our site.

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

* To personalize user’s experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
* To improve our website in order to better serve you.
* To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
* To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
* To quickly process your transactions.
* To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products
* To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)

**How do we protect visitor information?**

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

We use regular Malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order to maintain the safety of your personal information.

For your convenience, we may store your credit card information kept for more than 60 days in order to expedite future orders, and to automate the billing process.

**Do we use ‘cookies’?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We use cookies to:

* Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.
* Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits.
* Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer or Google Chrome) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

**If users disable cookies in their browser:**

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It will turn off some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.

**Third-party disclosure**

We may disclose personal information with third parties for a variety of purposes. We grant access to personal information to, for example, website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property or safety. We may share information with select, carefully selected business partners to make valuable offers tailored to your needs. You may opt out of sharing with our business partners **[here](https://lifeprotect247.com/help).**

Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third-party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-parties have separate and independent privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Disclosure**

The following disclosures are made pursuant to CalOPPA:

* Users can visit our site anonymously.
* Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes on our Privacy Policy Page
* Due to the variable nature of “Do Not Track” signals used by browsers as specified by the World Wide Web Consortium, we are not always able to honor the intent of a browser’s DNT mechanism.
* Users are able to change their personal information:

* By emailing us
* By calling us

* We allow third-party behavioral tracking.

**California Consumer Privacy Act**

The California Consumer Privacy Act requires specific disclosures and options for California consumers. Our CCPA disclosures are **[here](https://lifeprotect247.com/ccpa-policy).**

**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

We do not specifically market to children under 13, and do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe we have collected information regarding a child under 13 in error, please contact us below.

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

LifeProtect247.com

913 First Colonial Rd, Suite 204

Virginia Beach, VA 23454

United States

info@lifeprotect247.com

1-844-203-5617

### Ready to get started? Call us toll free.

Copyright © 2024 Life Protect 24/7, Inc.

|

|

|

[

](https://m.facebook.com/lifeprotect247)[

](https://mobile.twitter.com/lifeprotect247)[

](https://m.youtube.com/channel/UCBOiF2wHeFCVOPlOBQCKV5w?reload=9&skip_registered_account_check=true)
